{
  "samplequestions": [
    { "id": 1, "question": "Kotlin was developed by?", "optionOne" : "Facebook" , "optionTwo" : "Google", "optionThree": "JetBrains", "optionFour" : "Amazon", "correctAnswer" : 3 },
    { "id": 2, "question": "Which of following is used to handle null exceptions in Kotlin?" , "optionOne" : "if statement" , "optionTwo" : "Elvis Operator", "optionThree": "for loop", "optionFour" : "When", "correctAnswer" : 2  },
    { "id": 3, "question": "Which file extension is used to save Kotlin files." , "optionOne" : "kt extension" , "optionTwo" : "html", "optionThree": "SDK", "optionFour" : "javac", "correctAnswer" : 1  },
    { "id": 4, "question": "Which of the followings constructors are available in Kotlin?", "optionOne" : "Primary constructor" , "optionTwo" : "Init constructor", "optionThree": "Inner class", "optionFour" : "All above", "correctAnswer" : 1  },
    { "id": 5, "question": "What is an immutable variable?" , "optionOne" : "var a = 1" , "optionTwo" : "var b = 3 + a", "optionThree" : "var c = a + b", "optionFour" : "val d = c", "correctAnswer" : 4  },
    { "id": 6, "question": "What is correct way to create an arraylist in Kotlin?", "optionOne" : "val map = hashMapOf(1 to “one”, 2 to “two”, 3 to “three”)" , "optionTwo" : "enum class Color {RED, GREEN, BLUE}", "optionThree" : "val list = arrayListOf(1, 2, 3)", "optionFour" : "val set = hashSetOf(1, 2, 3)", "correctAnswer" : 3  },
    { "id": 7, "question": "Which of the following is not the basic data types in Kotlin?", "optionOne" : "Number" , "optionTwo" : "Boolean", "optionThree": "String", "optionFour" : "All above", "correctAnswer" : 4  },
    { "id": 8, "question": "Which one is our traning discord name?" , "optionOne" : "Android gang" , "optionTwo" : "Android master", "optionThree": "kotlin is my life", "optionFour" : "Super Android", "correctAnswer" : 1  },
    { "id": 9, "question": "What time our traning class start?" , "optionOne" : "12:00 pm" , "optionTwo" : "2:00 pm", "optionThree": "4:00 pm", "optionFour" : "6:00 pm", "correctAnswer" : 4  },
    { "id": 10, "question": "Who is our traning teacher??" , "optionOne" : "Byron" , "optionTwo" : "Seth", "optionThree": "Khaled", "optionFour" : "Thomas", "correctAnswer" : 4 }
  ],
  "profile": {
    "name": "team3Quiz"
  }
}
